Guide to the Olga Rudge Papers Addition
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1911-1996; Series I; 2.92; (7 boxes)
  - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE
    - De Scarpis family, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - De Zavia, Antoine, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Dickey, James, [1972] (Box 2, Folder 79)
      Transcription of sympathy note
    - Dieudonné, A., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Dioud, Assera Maria, 1976-80, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Di Suvero, Mariateresa, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - D'Offay, Anthony, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Duncan, Mabel, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Duran, Alex; Duran, Vera, 1962, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Du Sautoy, Peter, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Ede, Jim, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Egan, Desmond, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Eliot, Valerie, 1995, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Eudre, Otto, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Evans, Neil K., 1988 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - F.-, Jon and Stella, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Fang, Bernard, 1984-95 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Fani, Maria Luisa, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Favai, Maria, 1935, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Fiore, Maria Beggiata, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Fioula, Christine, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Fisher, Margaret, 1981-82 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Fitzgerald, Joan, 1963-91 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Fontana, Eros, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Foote, Toby, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Fox, Peggy, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Franchetti, Mimy, 1923, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Fry, Pauline; Simmesbach, Franz, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Gabrielli, Liana, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Gallup, Donald, 1987-95 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Gay, Harriet; Gay, Laurence, 1982-95, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Gerlin, Ruggero, n.d (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Giuseppe, F., 1961 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Goldsborough, Arnold, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Gonsalez-Jovec, Eladio, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Gowan, Robert Todd, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Grillone, Elisa Orzes, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Gueribe, Omar, 1961-71 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Gui Ping, Hu, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Hamblin, Dora Jane, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Hernandez, Hermilio, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - Hickey, Bernard, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - Hills, Diana and Jonathan, 1980-89, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Hoehs, Liselotte, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Hughes, Robert, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Hutchison, Kitty, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Inyoka, Nyota, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - Istituto Internazionale di Studi Musicali Comparati, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Italia, Maria, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - Jerdain, Charles, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Johnson, Kitty and Gwen, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Karbik, Cristine Nomi, 1975-79 (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Kaufman, Louis and Annette, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Kean, Katherine, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - Ketcham, John, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - Kleemann, Juerg, 1985 Oct 14 (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - Kozlowski, Rommy and Lydia, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - L.-, B., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - Laughlin, James, 1935-88, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Laura, Mary, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Lawton, Ralph, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - Levi, Raffaello, 1947-63 (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - Levy, Alan, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Liani, Davide, 1983, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Lodoli, Renzo, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Luciani, Sebastiano Arturo, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - Lussan, Régine, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - McDonald, Fred, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - McKeown, Rosalind and Tom, 1985 Aug 11 (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - MacMurraugh, Kilburn, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - MacShane, Frank, 1972-73, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Majno, Luigi, 1963-85, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - Manera, Giorgio, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - Manfredi, Antonio and Lidia (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - Mangione, Sofia, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - Martz, Louis, 1975-78 (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - Matz, Mary Jane, 1976-85, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - Maud, Ralph, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - Melton, Lindy, 1956 Sep 19 (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - Messinis, Mario, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - Milré, Jennifer and Yvon, 1973-93, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - Moneta, Gianni, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - Monghan, Melinda, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - Monnuti, G. P., n.d. (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - Mortari, Virgilio, 1947-53 (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - Muir, H. A., 1993 (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - Naaijkens, Els, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 163)
    - Niccoli, Julia; Nicoli, Raffaello, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - Noon, David, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - O'Donoghue, Catherine, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 166)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, 1987-96 (Box 3, Folder 167)
    - [Ostidich?], Alberto, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 168)
    - Ozturk, Tony, 1982, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 169)
    - Padilla, Eugenia Montero, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 170)
    - Pantano, Antonio, 1985-91, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 171)
    - Passante, N. [Hotel Gritti Palace Venezia], 1987 (Box 3, Folder 172)
    - Pastelliere, C., de Neuilly de la, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 173)
    - Paterson, Mary, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 174)
    - Pendleton, Eve, 1963-64 (Box 3, Folder 175)
    - Pescetto, Alberto, 1956-79, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 176)
    - Pirani, Max [Keith Falkner], 1962 (Box 3, Folder 177)
    - Pitkethly, Lawrence, 1982-83 (Box 3, Folder 178)
    - Poscia, Marie José, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 179)
    - Pound, Dorothy, 1968-72 (Box 3, Folder 180)
    - Pound, Ezra, 1925-[72], n.d. (Box 4, Folder 181-183)
    - Pound, Omar, 1972-95, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 184)
    - Proietti, Lidia, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 185)
    - Puccetti, Gabriella Aairo, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 186)
    - Quasimodo, Alessandro, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 187)
    - Quibitosi, Lorenza, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 188)
    - Quinn, Mary Bernetta, 1982-83, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 189)
    - Rainer, Dachine, 1984-95, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 190)
    - Ramsey, Gloria, 1963-95, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 191)
    - Raunio, Paul, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    - Redman, Tim, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 193)
      With note by Desmond O'Grady
    - Reid, Albert; Reid, Ethel, 1973-76, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 194)
    - Reid-Bowes, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 195)
    - Relladi, Manfredi, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 196)
    - Riewer, Eric, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 197)
    - Ritt, Ernst; Ritt, Maria, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 198)
    - Ritter, Fernando, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 199)
    - Roberts, F. W., 1971 (Box 4, Folder 200)
    - Romero, Phillip, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 201)
    - Rosso-Mazzinghi, Stefano, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 202)
    - Russell, Peter, 1967-72, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 203)
    - Rylands, Jane Turner, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 204)
      With photocopies of printed material
    - Sarto, Aldo, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 205)
    - Scheiwiller, Vanni, 1953-88, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 206)
    - Schwester, Hanny and Andreas, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 207)
    - Scotti, Antonietta, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 208)
    - Scotti, Lodovico Gallarati, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 209)
    - Secolo d'Italia, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 210)
    - Seferis, George, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 211)
    - Seguso, E., n.d. (Box 4, Folder 212)
    - Senititi, Guido, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 213)
    - Seyersted, Brita, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 214)
    - Shewring, Walter, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 215)
    - Siena, Pier Luigi, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 216)
    - Sigma-Tau, S.p.A. [Sigma Tau Pharmaceuticals], n.d. (Box 4, Folder 217)
    - Silvana, Francese, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 218)
    - Singh, Ghan Shyam; Singh, Gabrielle, 1978-95 (Box 4, Folder 219)
    - Solane, Janine, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 220)
    - Somers-Cocks, Blanche, 1948-53, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 221)
    - Stafford, Jack, 1968, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 222)
    - Stern, Dick, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 223)
    - Stocchi, Gabriele, 1978-86, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 224)
    - Storch, Laila, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 225)
    - Strale, Marguerite, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 226)
    - Stroumillo, Olga de (Nelly), 1978-87, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 227)
    - Surman, Diana, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 228)
    - Sutter, Jody, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 229)
    - Swabey, Henry, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 230)
    - Szasz, Thomas S., 1975-79, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 231)
    - Tani, Marco, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 232)
    - Terrell, Carroll F., 1985-86 (Box 5, Folder 233)
    - Thoresby, Christina, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 234)
    - Tiava, Tino, n.d (Box 5, Folder 235)
    - Todd, Ruthven, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 236)
    - Trimble, H. Burton, Jr., 1963 (Box 5, Folder 237)
    - V.-, Armando, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 238)
    - Vallerino, Elisa, 1962-65 (Box 5, Folder 239)
    - Van Buren, John, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 240)
    - Vezzoso, Dina, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 241)
    - Vidal, Gore, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 242)
    - Villa, Giancarlo; Villa, Shelagh, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 243)
    - Volpi, Anna Maria Cicogna, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 244)
    - Von Geruf, Lotte; Von Geruf, Hilda, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 245)
    - Waite, Robert G., 1985 (Box 5, Folder 246)
    - Wallace, Emily, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 247)
    - Wang, Lucien, Mrs., 1963 (Box 5, Folder 248)
    - Widershien, Marc; Widershien, Vita, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 249)
    - Widner, Brigitte, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 250)
    - Willis, Patricia, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 251)
    - Wykes-Joyce, Max, 1954-85 (Box 5, Folder 252)
    - Yagi, Mariyo, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 253)
    - Zampetti, Pietro, 1975, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 254)
    - Zaranella, Ab. Egidio, 1983, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 255)
    - Zennaro, Elena, 1973-95 (Box 5, Folder 256)
  - FIRST-NAME ONLY CORRESPONDENCE
    - Barbara, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 257)
    - Barbara and Euto, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 258)
    - Cecilia, 1962-63, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 259)
    - Charlotte, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 260)
    - Cheryl, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 261)
    - Claudio and Laura, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 262)
    - Elisabetta, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 263)
    - Elizabeth and Ian, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 264)
    - Eva (Box 5, Folder 265)
    - Frances [and Ashley], 1985 (Box 5, Folder 266)
    - Gianfranco and Sousha, 1974-75 (Box 5, Folder 267)
    - Jacques, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 268)
    - Jane, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 269)
    - Jean, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 270)
    - Kathleen, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 271)
    - Lindi (Box 5, Folder 272)
    - Lucia, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 273)
    - Marc, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 274)
    - Martha, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 275)
    - Melisa et. al., n.d. (Box 5, Folder 276)
    - Nina, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 277)
    - Peter, 1949-95, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 278)
    - Roberta, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 279)
    - Rosalind and Thomas, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 280)
    - Rudi et. al., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 281)
    - Sarah, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 282)
    - Sophia, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 283)
    - Stefano et. al., 1995 (Box 5, Folder 284)
    - Suzan, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 285)
    - Tsamu, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 286)
    - Vinny, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 287)
  - BIRTHDAY TELEGRAMS AND EMPTY ENVELOPES
    - Telegrams to Olga Ridge for her 100th Birthday, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 288)
    - Unidentified, 1926-84, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 289)
    - Empty Envelopes, 1939-91, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 290-293)
  - THIRD PARTY CORRESPONDENCE
    - Baillon, Jacques to Régine Lussan, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 294)
    - Beals, Walter B. to Ezra Pound (Box 6, Folder 295)
    - Bennett, Alma to Mary de Rachewiltz, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 296)
    - Bridson, Geoffrey to Mary de Rachewiltz, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 297)
    - Cadorin, Guido to Ezra Pound, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 298)
    - Cadorin, Guido to unidentified, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 299)
    - Caico, Lina to Ezra Pound, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 300)
    - Casella, Alfredo to Ezra Pound, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 301)
    - Cherokee, Francis to Ezra Pound, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 302)
    - Cleaveland, Dorothy [J.S. Dickey] to Norman Hood, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 303)
    - Clinique "La Prairie" to Ezra Pound, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 304)
    - Comune di Zoagli to Ezra Pound, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 305)
    - Connolly, Cyril to Ezra Pound, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 306)
    - D. to M., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 307)
    - Dazzi, Manilo to Ezra Pound, 1938-42 (Box 6, Folder 308)
    - De Barbieri, Vittoria to Gabriella, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 309)
    - De La Inoferiali to Ezra Pound, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 310)
    - De Luigi, Ludovico to Mary de Rachewiltz, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 311)
    - Dondo, Mathurin to Ezra Pound (Box 6, Folder 312)
    - Driver, Clive to Ezra Pound, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 313)
    - Eliot, Valerie and Eliot, T. S. ("Possum") to Dorothy and Ezra Pound (Box 6, Folder 314)
    - Fang, Achilles to Ezra Pound, 1947-48 (Box 6, Folder 315)
    - Favai, Gennaro and Maria to Lisa, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 316)
    - Forschungsinstitut für Kulturmorphologie to Ezra Pound, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 317)
    - Fravili, Carlo to Mary de Rachewiltz, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 318)
    - Gaietta, L.- to Ezra Pound, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 319)
    - Habbah, Abraham to Ezra Pound, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 320)
    - Haworth-Booth, Mark to Ezra Pound, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 321)
    - Herlitschka, Heberth E. to Ezra Pound, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 322)
    - Hickey, Bernard and Ghan Shyam Singh to Il Gazzettino di Venezia, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 323)
    - Hickok, Guy to Ezra Pound, 1931 (Box 6, Folder 324)
    - [Ivancich, Adriana] to Ezra Pound (Box 6, Folder 325)
    - Ivar et. al. to Maria Rudge, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 326)
    - Kodama, Sanehide to Ezra Pound (Box 6, Folder 327)
    - L.-, M.- to Ezra Pound, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 328)
    - L.-, W. A. to Ezra Pound, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 329)
    - La Driere, Craig to Ezra Pound, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 330)
    - Laughlin, James to Ezra Pound, 1948-61 (Box 6, Folder 331)
    - Lauritano, Giuseppe to Giogio Lorno, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 332)
    - Liushoeft, Hans and Brigitte to Ezra Pound, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 333)
    - Longo, Giorgio to Famiglia Pound, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 334)
    - "Louise" to Mr. and Mrs. G. T. Slavin, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 335)
    - "Luigi" to Ezra Pound, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 336)
    - M.- to Mary de Rachewiltz, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 337)
    - McBride, Stewart Dill to Mary de Rachewiltz, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 338)
    - Mathes, James R. to Mary de Rachewiltz, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 339)
    - Munson, Gorham to The New Masses, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 340)
    - "Mother" to "Doug", 1947 (Box 6, Folder 341)
    - Nixon, David to Ezra Pound (Box 6, Folder 342)
    - Ostidich, Alberto to unidentified, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 343)
    - Palazzo Grassi [Centro Internazionale delle Arti e del Costume] to Ezra Pound, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 344)
    - Picot, Max to Ezra Pound, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 345)
    - Pilkington, Walter to Ezra Pound, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 346)
    - Pole, Major D. Graham to Ezra Pound, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 347)
    - Polignac, Winaretta de to Ezra Pound, 1939 Mar (Box 6, Folder 348)
    - Polverelli, G. to Ezra Pound, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 349)
    - Por, Odon to Ezra Pound (Box 6, Folder 350)
    - Pound, Dorothy to Ezra Pound, 1962-72 (Box 6, Folder 351)
    - Pound, Ezra to Mrs. F. A. Beyda, 1911 (Box 7, Folder 352)
    - Pound, Ezra to Renata Borgatti (Box 7, Folder 353)
    - Pound, Ezra to Guido Cadorin, 1968-71 (Box 7, Folder 354)
    - Pound, Ezra to Uwe Dick, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 355)
    - Pound, Ezra to Clive Driver, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 356)
    - Pound, Ezra to Le Figaro Litteraire (Paris), 1965 (Box 7, Folder 357)
    - Pound Ezra to Donald Gallup (Box 7, Folder 358)
    - Pound, Ezra to O. B. Hardison, Jr. (Box 7, Folder 359)
    - Pound, Ezra to Father Hoehn (Box 7, Folder 360)
    - Pound, Ezra to James Laughlin (Box 7, Folder 361)
    - Pound, Ezra to Mary de Rachewiltz (Box 7, Folder 362)
    - Pound, Ezra to Tibor Serly (Box 7, Folder 363)
    - Pound, Ezra to the Supreme Court of the United States (Box 7, Folder 364)
    - Pound, Ezra to Walter (Box 7, Folder 365)
    - Pound, Ezra to unidentified (Box 7, Folder 366)
    - Rachewiltz, Mary de to Stewart Dill McBride, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 367)
    - Rachewiltz, Mary de to Homer L. Pound ["Nonno"] (Box 7, Folder 368)
    - Rachewiltz, Mary de to Vanni Scheiwiller, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 369)
    - Reschke, Lyning to Ezra Pound, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 370)
    - Rohmann, Egon to Ezra Pound, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 371)
    - Rudolf, Dr. Direcktor to Accadmia Musicale Chigiana Siena, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 372)
    - S.-, R.- to Ezra Pound, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 373)
    - Sauter, Rudolf to Ezra Pound, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 374)
    - Something Else Press to Ezra Pound (Box 7, Folder 375)
    - Solane, Dominique Janine to Ezra Pound, 1966-67 (Box 7, Folder 376)
    - Soto, Ken to Ezra Pound, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 377)
    - Stocchi, Gabriele to Ezra Pound, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 378)
    - Studer, Clara to Dorothy Pound, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 379)
    - Taupin, Renè to Ezra Pound (Box 7, Folder 380)
    - Terrell, Carroll F. to Professor Ricci, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 381)
    - Titus, Edward W. to Ezra Pound, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 382)
    - Uberti, R. degli to Piero Magi, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 383)
    - Ufficio Registro Abbonamenti Radio-TV to Ezra Pound, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 384)
    - Vecchi, Professor Giuseppe to Ezra Pound, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 385)
    - Wagner, Charles A. to Ezra Pound, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 386)
    - Waters, Alan to John Drummond, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 387)
    - Weber, John to Ezra Pound (Box 7, Folder 388)
    - White, D. to unidentified, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 389)
    - Whittaker, W. Gillies to Ezra Pound, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 390)
    - Willis, Patricia C. to Régine Lussan, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 391)
    - Wright, David to Ghan Shyam Singh, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 392)
    - Unidentified to Ezra Pound, 1912-87, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 393)
    - Unidentified fragments, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 394)
    - Empty envelopes, 1931-90, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 395)
- Personal Papers, 1867-1996; Series II; 2.51; (6 boxes)
  Series II, Personal Papers, is arranged alphabetically by type of material.
  - Address book, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 396)
  - Address slips and telephone numbers (Box 8, Folder 397)
  - Agendas, 1925-80 (Box 8, Folder 398-402)
  - Album: green, 1867-1935, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 403-410)
  - Album: green, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 411)
  - Album: red, 1930-82, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 412-417)
  - Album: red, 1930-82, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 418-424)
  - Album: red, 1930-82, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 425-432)
  - Architectural drawings, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 433)
  - Birth certificate, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 434)
  - Calling cards, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 435)
    Related Archival Materials note
    See also: Oversize, Box 51, folder 1186
  - Death certificates of Ezra Pound, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 436)
  - Diaries, 1989, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 437)
  - "Diploma di Collaborazione", 1957
  - Empty envelopes, 1974-90, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 438)
  - Financial Papers
    - Bank statements and receipts, 1945-82, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 439-444)
  - Bills and receipts: general, 1952-87, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 445-454)
    - Bills and receipts: utilities, 1954-88 (Box 10, Folder 455-462)
    - Checks and checkbook stubs, 1968-89 (Box 10, Folder 463-465)
    - Tax forms and tax receipts, 1960-77 (Box 10, Folder 466-470)
  - I Ching notes and cards, 1985 Sep-Nov (Box 11, Folder 471)
  - Idaho Ezra Pound museum plans
    - Correspondence, 1972-75 (Box 11, Folder 472)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1973-76, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 473)
    - Notes, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 474)
    - Printed material, 1972, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 475)
  - Inventories: books, manuscripts, tapes, clippings, and photos (Box 11, Folder 476)
  - Inventories: household items, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 477)
  - Invitations and announcements, 1978-89, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 478)
  - Itineraries and schedules, 1979, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 479)
  - Legal Papers
    - Damage claims against Allied Forces, 1943-58 (Box 11, Folder 480)
    - Ezra Pound Literary Trust, 1949-82 (Box 11, Folder 481)
    - Interview release for New York Center for Visual History, 1982, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 482)
    - Lease for 252 Dorsoduro, 1960 May 26 (Box 11, Folder 483)
    - Probate court documents concerning estate of Elizabeth Templeton, 1894-1910, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 484)
    - United States Overseas Census Report, 1960, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 485)
    - Will (draft), 1985 March 30 (Box 11, Folder 486)
    - Unidentified and misc. (Box 11, Folder 487)
  - Letter drafts: unidentified and incomplete, 1959-79, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 488)
  - Lists: names, 1972-80, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 489)
  - Lists: to-do, 1977-86, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 490)
  - Medical information, 1927-69, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 491)
  - Membership cards, 1920-81 (Box 11, Folder 492)
  - Memorabilia
    - Annotated clipping, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 493)
    - Annotated map of Siena, 1970, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 494)
    - Baggage claim sticker, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 495)
    - Book signed by friends for Olga Rudge's 100th birthday, 1986-96 (Box 12, Folder 496)
    - Card with inscription, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 497)
    - Christmas banner, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 498)
    - Cookbooks, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 499-500)
    - Handkerchief and cameo of Franz Pesapane (with Christmas greeting), 1931 Dec 10 (Box 12, Folder 501)
    - Matchbook covers from Spoleto, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 502)
    - Menus, 1986, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 503)
    - Pages from Homer Pound's dictionary (front cover and title page), 1934 (Box 12, Folder 504)
    - Postcards (blank and annotated) (Box 12, Folder 505)
    - Pressed flowers, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 506)
    - Ticket stubs, 1925-87, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 507)
    - Train tickets, 1971, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 508)
    - Travel brochure from Furnes, 1903 (Box 12, Folder 509)
    - Unidentified and miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 510)
  - Notebooks, 1908-28 (Box 12, Folder 511)
  - Notebooks, 1936-55 (Box 12, Folder 512)
  - Notebooks, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 513)
  - Notebooks, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 514)
  - Notes: books and authors (Box 13, Folder 515)
  - Notes: miscellaneous, 1923-88, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 516)
  - Notes: music, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 517)
  - Notes: Vivaldi, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 518)
  - Notes on Pound
    - Biographical, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 519)
    - Cantos, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 520)
    - Exhibits and tributes (Box 13, Folder 521)
    - Writings, 1966-73, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 522)
    - Yeats-Pound memorial (Box 13, Folder 523)
    - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 524)
  - Passports and identity cards, 1917-56, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 525)
  - Recipes, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 526)
  - Scrapbook, 1913-31, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 527)
  - Sketches, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 528)
  - Writings: "Agenda" (Box 13, Folder 529)
  - Writings: letters to the editor, 1976-78, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 530)
  - Writings: "Money Talks", n.d. (Box 13, Folder 531)
  - Writings: "La settimane musicali di Siena", 1962 (Box 13, Folder 532)
  - Writings: unidentified, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 533-534)
- Rudge Family Papers, 1819-1991; Series III; 0.63; (2 boxes)
  Series III, Rudge Family Papers, is organized into three subseries: Correspondence with Olga Rudge, Third-Party Correspondence, and Family Papers.
  - CORRESPONDENCE WITH OLGA RUDGE
    - Baynes, Ernest Harold, 1904 Jan 3 (Box 14, Folder 535)
    - Heacock, Priscilla W., 1956 Aug 29 (Box 14, Folder 536)
    - Maline, Julian L., 1929, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 537)
    - Rudge, Arthur, 1911, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 538)
    - Rudge, George, 1904 Dec 25 (Box 14, Folder 539)
    - Rudge, J. Edgar, 1907 Apr 23 (Box 14, Folder 540)
    - Rudge, Julia O'Connell, 1907-18, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 541)
    - Rudge, Peter, 1955-72 (Box 14, Folder 542)
    - Rudge, Teddy, 1918, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 543)
    - Unidentified, 1902-91, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 544)
  - THIRD PARTY CORRESPONDENCE
    - Addison, R.B. to Julia O'Connell Rudge, 1909, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 545)
    - Baynes, Louise to Arthur Rudge, 1910 Sep 27 (Box 14, Folder 546)
    - Baynes, Louise to Teddy Rudge, 1936 Jun-Aug (Box 14, Folder 547)
    - Ethel to Julia O'Connell Rudge, 1912 Aug 20 (Box 14, Folder 548)